RG 071:003, Department of Housing Planning Maps
Connecticut State Library
- Dept. of Community Affairs. Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980
  - East Haddam (Box 4)
    - Street and traffic circulation, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Community facilities, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 43.5 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Community facilities, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 43.5 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Buildable land map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42 x 47 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Buildable land map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42 x 47 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Neighborhood boundaries, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42 x 47 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Neighborhood boundaries, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42 x 47 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Zoning map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.5 x 46.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
  - East Hartford (Box 4)
    - Zoning map, undated; Goodkind & O'Dea Planning Consultants; 18.75 x 23.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: Business I-A
    - Zone plan, 1950 March; Engineering Department, East Hartford; 24 x 22 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Zone plan, 1953 September; Engineering Department, East Hartford; 24 x 22 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
  - East Haven (Box 4)
    - Building zone map, 1958 April 8; Robert H. Decker; 36 x 25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Existing topography, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Borings and surficial geology, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Acquisition map, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Existing land use and zoning, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Proposed streets and grading, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 5
    - Storm drainage system, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 6
    - Sanitary sewer system, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 7
    - Water system, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 8
    - Gas system, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 9
    - Electric & telephone system, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 10
    - Disposition map, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 11
    - Proposed land use, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 12
    - Proposed zoning, 1974 July; Flaherty and Giavara Associates; 48 x 32 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 13
  - East Windsor (Box 4)
    - Base map, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
      701 project: Conn. P-64
    - Topography, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Comprehensive plan, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Population distribution, 1966 April; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Community facilites, 1967 May; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Existing land use, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Neighborhood areas, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Traffic and transportation, 1967 May; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Zoning map, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 42 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Town plan base map, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 39 x 44.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 1 Utilities, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 2 Land growth trends, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 4 Physical information, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 4 Soils, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 4b Marginal land, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 5 Circulation traffic volume, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 6 Industrial development, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - 8 Zoning map, undated; Pedersen and Tilney; 42.25 x 65 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - Summary digest comprehensive plan, 1967; E. H Lord-Wood Associates (Box 4)
    - Report on subdivision regulations, undated; Pedersen and Tilney (Box 4)
  - Ellington (Box 4)
    - Base map area of influence, 1966 December 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 22 x 30.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
      701 project: Conn. P-57
    - Street map, 1966 December 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 66 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Topography map, 1966 December 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 66 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Town center map, 1967 May 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 26.5 x 45.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Generalized land use, 1967 January 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 22 x 30.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Traffic volume map, 1967 January 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 22 x 30.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Population map, 1967 January 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 22 x 30.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Generalized zoning, 1967 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 22 x 30.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Exsisting land use, 1967 May 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Population density map, 1967 May 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Buildable land map, 1967 April 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Thoroughfare map, 1967 January 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Traffic volumes, 1967 January 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Water resources, 1967 May 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
    - Proposed land use, 1966 January 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: 4-A
    - Town center, 1967 May 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 26.5 x 45.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Zoning map, 1966 December 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 64.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: V-B
    - Report - community monographs, 1971 June (Box 4)
  - Essex (Box 4)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 41.5 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
      701 project: Conn. P-9
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 35.5 x 39 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 35.5 x 39 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 35.5 x 39 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Plan of development, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 36.25 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 4)
    - General land use, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Manufacturing and employment, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Labor force, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Retail trade, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 4)
    - Topography, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: IV-a
    - Drainage areas, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: IV-b
    - Swamps and steep slopes, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: IV-c
    - Soils, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: IV-d
    - Conditions affecting development, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: IV-e
    - Land use, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: V-a
    - Land use, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 4)
    - Land use, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 4)
    - Land use, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 4)
    - Neighborhoods, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: VI-a
    - Population distribution, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
    - School population distribution, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
    - Public facilities, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
    - Water mains, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: X-a
    - Traffic flow, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
      plan number: XII-a
    - Pilot plan, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 4)
    - Schematic street pattern, 1970 March; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 22.5 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 4)
    - Essex village, undated; E. H Lord-Wood Associates; 26 x 31 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 4)
  - Fairfield (Box 5)
    - Zoning districts, 1970 October 1; 27 x 23 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: M14
  - Farmington (Box 5)
    - Proposed circulation, undated; Town Planning Department; 17 x 21.5 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing land use map, 1962 October; Town Planning Department; 17 x 21.5 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Plan of development, 1964 June; Town Planning Department; 22.75 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 1500 feet (Box 5)
  - Glastonbury (Box 5)
    - Building - zoning map, 1956 June 25; John J. Mozzochi; 21 x 32.25 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Building - zoning map, 1956 June 25; John J. Mozzochi; 21 x 32.25 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Building - zoning map, 1956 June 25; John J. Mozzochi; 21 x 32.25 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Development policies map, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Development policies map, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Utilities map, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Utilities map, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing and proposed circulation, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing and proposed circulation, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing curbs and sidewalks, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing curbs and sidewalks, 1969 November; Brown, Donald and Donald; 48 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Plan of development, 1970 January 1; Brown, Donald and Donald; 21.5 x 29 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
  - Goshen (Box 5)
    - Comprehensive plan of development, 1959 June 1; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 40 x 30 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Zoning map, 1959 June 1; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 40 x 30 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: F-3
  - Granby (Box 5)
    - Topographic map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 41.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Soils map, 1962 May; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: II-B-1
    - Drainage basins, swamps, flood prone land, 1962 May; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing land uses, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Steep slopes map, 1962 May; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Conditions of buildability, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Evaluation of conditions affecting buildability of land, Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Population projection, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 28.5 x 21.5 in. (Box 5)
      plan number: II-F
    - Population growth and projections, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Population distribution map, 1962 October 26; Technical Planning Associates; 41.25 x 34.75 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: II-F-1
    - Pilot plan of development, 1963 March; Technical Planning Associates; 21.25 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 5)
    - Circulation plan, 1963 March; Technical Planning Associates; 21.25 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 5)
    - Plan of Granby center, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 36.75 x 27.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-C-2
    - Public facilites - schools, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 21.25 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 5)
  - Greenwich (Box 5)
    - Public and semi-public uses, 1975 February 2; Planning and Zoning Commission; 56 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
  - Groton (Box 5)
    - Area of influence, Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 14.5 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 5)
      701 project: Conn. P-15
    - General pattern of land use, 1960 Decemeber 31; Technical Planning Associates; 18.75 x 14.5 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 5)
    - Neighborhood areas, 1960 July; Technical Planning Associates; 24.5 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      701 project: Conn. P-13
    - Drainage basins, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 30 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing land use, 1960 Decemeber 31; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-A-1
    - Residential development Jan 1951-Dec 1960, Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
    - Suitability of land for development, 1960 Decemeber 31; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Population distribution by neighborhoods, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Recreational facilities plan, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-E-3
    - Existing and proposed schools, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-E-4
    - Elementary schools, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Public water supply, 1960 Decemeber 31; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-F-1
    - Sewer service, 1960 Decemeber 31; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-F-2
    - Land use plan, 1961 May; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Circulation plan, 1961 May; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Plan of commerce and industry, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Plan of residential areas, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - General subdivision plan, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 19 x 47 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: V-A
    - Zoning map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: VI-A
    - Community facilities plan, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24.5 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Zoning map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 24.5 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 5)
    - Improvement & extension of Conn. 117, 1968 September 30; Aero Service Corporation; 32 x 61 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: 1 of 1
    - Improvement & extension of Conn. 117, 1968 September 30; Aero Service Corporation; 31 x 58.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: 1-A of 9
    - Plan of development pamphlet, 1960; Technical Planning Associates (Box 5)
  - Guilford (Box 5)
    - Base map, 1965 January; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 84.5 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
      701 project: Conn. P-49
      plan number: I-A-I
    - Map A - land use and circulation plan, 1965 October; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 84.5 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Map B - public facilies and open space plan, 1965 October; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 84.5 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Town Marina improvements- Plot plan, 1967 January 3; Russell W. Waldo; 24 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 20 feet (Box 5)
    - Plan proposed, 1967 January 3; Russell W. Waldo; 24 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 20 feet (Box 5)
    - Section and details, 1967 January 3; Russell W. Waldo; 24 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 20 feet (Box 5)
    - Town Marina improvements, 1967 January 3; Russell W. Waldo; 24 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 20 feet (Box 5)
    - Utilities plan, 1967 January 3; Russell W. Waldo; 24 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 20 feet (Box 5)
    - Town map - open space plan, 1972 May 1; Guilford Planning & Zoning Commission; 42 x 21.5 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 5)
  - Haddam (Box 5)
    - Zoning map, 1961; 22 x 17 in.; 1.5 inch = 1 mile (Box 5)
  - Hamden (Box 5)
    - Zoning map, 1950 February 7; 41 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
  - Hebron (Box 5)
    - Area of influence base map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 5)
      701 project: Conn. P-37
    - Street map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Building location map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Topography, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Town center base map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 80 feet (Box 5)
    - Amston lake area base map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 300 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: I-F
    - Generalized land use, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 5)
    - Traffic volumes, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 5)
    - Population, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 5)
    - Buildable land, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Generalized zoning, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 5)
    - Existing land use, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing land use, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 80 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing land use lake Amston area, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 300 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-B-X
    - General soils, 1964 June 1; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
      plan number: III-C-X
    - Population density, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Thoroughfares, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Traffic flow, 1964 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Proposed land use & community facilities, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Town center proposed land use, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 80 feet (Box 5)
    - Amston Lake proposed land use, 1965 February 1; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 46.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 300 feet (Box 5)
    - Wetland soil survey, 1974 July 22; 42.5 x 29.25 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Zoning map, 1977 June 14; 36 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 5)
    - Land use plan, 1980; 34.5 x 22.5 in. (Box 5)
    - Town roads, undated; 10 x 15.5 in. (Box 5)
  - Killingly (Box 5)
    - Zoning map, 21.75 x 16.75 in. (Box 5)
  - Killingworth (Box 5)
    - Killingworth center map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 40.5 x 20.25 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 5)
    - Topography map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 51.5 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Buildable land map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 51.5 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Existing land use map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Proposed zoning map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Watershed map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Roads & traffic map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Land use & highway plan, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Public facilities plan, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Base map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
    - Dwelling unit map, 1967 July; Raymond & May Associates; 67.25 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 5)
  - Lyme (Box 6)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Zoning map, 1964 June; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Plan of development, 1964 June; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Land suitability map, 1964 June; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Conditions affecting development, 1964 June; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Existing land use, 1964 June; Technical Planning Associates; 42.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
  - Manchester (Box 6)
    - Base map, 1960; Planning and renewal Associates; 45 x 41 in.; 1 inch = 9600 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed sewer system improvements, undated; Planning and renewal Associates; 45 x 41 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 6)
      701 project: Conn. P-18
    - Proposed water system improvements, undated; Planning and renewal Associates; 45 x 41 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed land use and circulation pattern, undated; Planning and renewal Associates; 45 x 41 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed zoning districts, undated; Planning and renewal Associates; 45 x 41 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 6)
    - CBD base map, undated; Planning and renewal Associates; 24 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Existing land use, 1960; Planning and renewal Associates; 24 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)